So we create an extension of only files, right?
Because if I go to any website, I can press no to I see about the images.
It can even export the table directly from here.
So we detect some table and it will try to export the Excels file, right?
So here we have a column interpolation execution.
And if I press the node all again, I can go on with PNG files.
And then I can go on now.
And if I was on the side, but I still see other things like pages.
All right.
I would like to scrap it.
For example, a shops.
So it will just not only need a node, but scrap too.
So I have an extension we'll use as an inspiration, which is easy scraper.
So it will automatically detect some of the pages.
You see smartphones.
And then we can try to set.
If you allow us to scrap list, our can type is a scraper.
So if you want, click web scraper.
You see they have their own website.
I have to Chrome.
It's actually very common.
I have a website for its own Chrome extension.
So I will now try to do it.
I will open cursor and now open my previous agents.
So what I can do, I can copy over the easy scraper.
Go again to cursor.
Open new agents.
I want you to add functionality.
That will allow us to scrape the website and turn scraping out the tool.
Try to select a part of the website.
Such as div.
All right.
It should work.
Obviously, you might actually import any additional things.
Here we have a background.
We have some folders that are not longer used.
So let's use it.
And open new agent.
Here I'm used files and folders.
So it'll just be local.
And I'll post the video and return when extension is ready.
We have it ready.
You can see the changes.
It removed the new files.
So we had like a free folders.
And this is the scrapping functionality.
So we have a JavaScript and pop up.
All right.
So if I further do it, I'll just go to my manager extension tab.
I'll go to the very left.
I'll refresh it.
Maybe I'll try to use it again on different side.
Start scraping, for example, chapter.
Okay.
We have the functionality, but it's not working.
Not well, so we'll just edit.
And okay.
But after I select one element, try to find similar elements on the site.
And when it's here, fill it up.
And allow us to download in Excel X.
CS file extension.
Plus, a skip button is not working.
And I want to cancel the scrapping.
We have a new element, a new variable.
Most of it will be stored, let me try.
Now we'll go again, refresh.
So we'll refresh my extension.
I open my, maybe I'll try to look for something similar.
I just want it to be socially normal person.
I think it will be hard to describe.
But I can use like a scrapping test website.
Now there's one about books.
So we can use the scraper.
And this is the test one.
Let's try to look.
Now we have a top items being scrapped now.
And what I can do now, I can press the node, start scraping.
And yeah.
Actually found similar elements, it's scrapping automatically.
The problem is that my escape is now working, which is great.
And the other thing is just okay, have an element.
So it's a title.
All right.
Let's get it. It gets export to Excel.
And we have a, it's nicely done perfectly.
You can change it a little bit because this one is automatically scraping.
In that extension here, we have to kind of press it.
So now if you want to get like a views,
you do try to use.
And but we still have to click on the side.
I can clear everything, the scraper and press again.
And for elements, we can export to see is from file,
which is the review account.
But I would like to have it in like at the bottom, not only when I click.
So I will add for additional feature.
This one is okay.
We can leave it actually.
It's handy.
So there are no tables.
So for now, what I'm going to do.
I'll go again to cursor.
Looks great.
But I want to add a small module or window on the right.
When I'm in scrapping model,
that will allow me to preview market similar elements.
And add bottom.
That will allow me to scrape the enemy fleet without clicking on the extension.
Again, to open a window and scrub this selected elements.
All right.
It's done.
I will open it again.
It will first and extension.
The money is refreshed.
I will go to my scraping.
And I will go here.
I can clear all.
And I can start scraping.
And we see I have a chart.
Elements titles.
And it's pretty much it.
And when I press escape, it's turn offs again.
But as we can see, the scrapping monkey element presses.
So now I'll go again to cursor.
Scrapically, I press data exit.
It doesn't piece up here.
I'm doing it when I'm scraping elements.
And as a window on the right,
the window disappears.
But not that's a top message.
And make that window on the right.
Display under a bar.
Chars.
Preview text.
OK.
We have just number of characters.
So it's not that well for us.
So it will just display it while the counter scrape.
Fix them on the persistence.
Now the sidebar.
And then move the character combo, the preview text.
OK.
I will return now refresh the extension.
Let me clear.
OK.
This is on safety scrap.
Now refresh.
I don't see any errors.
And let me try it again.
I'll clear all of the data.
Now you start web scraping.
And yeah, I have a title.
I says prom, which is the grade.
And I can select all.
Select all, doesn't work well.
You can see the script selected.
It will not show.
So I'll add a new feature again.
I open a cursor.
And what I'm going to do, I need the thing that
select all in the right.
But it's not working.
And scrape selected as we can see here.
And select that should be grayed out.
Here there is the num elements selected.
OK.
It should work.
We see actually how it looks like.
Let me try to find this.
OK.
The similar elements.
X button doesn't work either, too.
But escape works.
So again.
And X button to close.
Right.
The panel is not working either.
I open a new agent.
That's why, because it's already heavily context.
And they will be like another fixes or features to our
Chrome extension.
OK.
I'll refresh it again.
I'll open it up.
Now we use the normal extension.
I will start scraping automatically detected many things.
But apparently I just want to scrap.
OK.
Maybe I'll just use the start scraping and then close the window
here, because it just doesn't look well.
So if I start or start, it should automatically close.
Let me have some elements.
But if I press X, it's still not working.
So we have to ask it again.
Let me see if actually the fire that I'm the node.
It has some data.
We have a data.
And we'll do something else.
We have a function output from the main window related to scrapping.
And just leave the button.
Start scraping.
That will close.
And then pop up window and open right panel.
That will display a similar elements when we click on something.
Let's add a button.
On the right, on both the output data types.
We have four to those simplified pop-up to just remove the UI.
It's created actually.
Made it because it probably has all changed on.
Plan as well here.
But it's all right.
We can do it this way.
So it's fine.
So let's add the output to detect even missing there.
And implement the output data types function.
Obviously we can try to look for other functions.
Or maybe it was other I had to implement this module.
But for now, it will be enough.
Now if I just extension, I will refresh.
Open your agent instead of X, bottom, and output detect.
I can maybe remove rename similar elements to scraping elements.
And remove X with bottom, and output detect bottom switch.
I can do a button with text.
Did you feel it with quicker?
Okay, we have another issue.
When I use frames selected, it's not being downloaded.
And output detect is not fitting.
But from border, please, please, add that top banner that we are in selecting mode.
Okay, hope it will work now.
Okay, and we'll refresh again.
We will web scrape now press and start scrape.
Oh, I see now the elements looks nice.
And if I press it, scrubbing mode, selecting.
And I will just scrape selected.
It's downloading.
And if I press escape, if I waste the resume, press escape to quit.
Perfect.
And we don't know all data.
And this is what I wanted.
So we created a nice extension.
And probably we could add another features like scrap with CS file and Excel X.
But still it's enough because this one don't know it with JSON.
And we basically don't need to relate that much on JSON.
But we can obviously open it up and see the data here.
Okay, so the footage has probably implemented functionality related to export types and different data.
But for now, it will be enough.
So we have a scraping.
If you go to any page, like even here project game and Gemini protocol.
Some news.
And maybe I'll open like some blog post.
This is the GitHub.
Yeah, I'm always in the GitHub.
Now we have images.
And here directly I see add items to a list.
You can download on and if you don't all of the images directly from here.
And if I go to Wikipedia.
I will go here.
This is the city in what's the table here.
If I open it, we see the table with columns.
We can as well add a feature when we hover in the table.
It will basically scroll down to it.
So it will just let us know which table is it.
But yeah, this way we can actually create.
You can even export all of the extra because if I export all of the types,
so it will export.
And that table.
So we have all of the information directly from here.